Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas.
What was uh what's practice like on
Christmas Eve?
Any different?
No different.
No different. Just working. Yeah.
When you look at Arizona's defense, what
what kind of Zach says they kind of will
play you in unique ways than other
teams. What makes them unique?
Yeah, they don't do
um the traditional
coverages that you typically see.
They do, but they get to them from
different ways.
They're going to play uh
kind of umbrella
look from the secondary and
roll and drop into a bunch of different
coverages.
Um it it kind of reminds me of how
Clemson kind of played us in the
national championship.
Um
so it'll present a unique challenge for
sure.
What was it like getting, you know, I
guess given everything that's happened
to you this year, what's it like to win
player of the week week 17 16?
Yeah, I played well. Cool.
Um done that a lot.
It's uh
it's good to
get a win and and play well and
um
find some happiness.
What's it been like learning to figure
out double double coverages over the
years? Yeah, it's been a process.
Um
[Music]
and we have we have so many weapons now
that
um
teams will still do it, but we have so
many different ways to attack it now.
Our coaches do such a good job of
designing couple plays each week to to
go and beat it and
um we face it enough now that we can
make adjustments on the fly when we see
it.
Especially if you see it a lot in the
game.
And you know, Mike G's been
a big part of that. Chase Brown has been
a big part of that out of the backfield
when we can recognize it. Andre's played
a big role in that. So
we have so many guys now that can go and
beat
man coverage that
teams can't just sit in it like that. I
I used to
run teams out of it with my legs and
then they they started to spy a little
bit, so I stopped doing that and you
know, I'm not running too much this
year.
Um
but like I said, our coaches do such a
good job of designing
plays and game plans for
all the unique kind of things that we
see because of those two guys.
Um
that we we get put in really good spots.
For a lack of a better way to say is it
like an honor that teams will throw
double double looks at you that they
won't do against any other team in the
league? Yeah, I mean those guys
I think
certainly take that as a sign of respect
as you should.
Um
Teams that haven't showed that on tape
will
throw that out there against us and
it's cuz nobody can cover those guys
one-on-one.
Um
unless they have some kind of help
somewhere in funneling them. So
but like I said, we have so many
different ways to beat it now. It seems
like you're
like you will throw it into the double
double sometimes with those guys too.
You have a lot of confidence in them
that I mean
all the Jamal was
Yeah, we have we have certain routes
that we feel good about still
uh against that coverage cuz you can't
just
let teams double them and
then say uh those guys are out of the
game plan now.
They're too good of players to
to think that way. You still have to
find ways to get them the ball
and we've seen it enough now that we can
get get to that on the fly and
attack it. How do you do it? How do you
get them How do you throw it into the
double coverage without it?
Um well, usually has to be some kind of
double move. Something like that. You
have talked about the mobility. How has
it been now a few weeks games playing on
the toe? How's the toe felt? Yeah, it
feels good.
Certainly not as mobile as I have been
in the past, but mobile enough to to
make a couple plays every game.
Certainly not going to make a living
doing it right now, but
I've been able to be effective in spots.
I saw you switch shoes. Any reason why
you went back to what you were
previously wearing? Those were a little
more comfortable. Yeah, you feel like is
it now just where you is it you
progressed far enough that we can go
back to it? Is that part of it or is
Yeah, I think I think that's fair to
say. Yeah.
What have you seen from your guys'
defense improvements since the bye week?
Yeah, it's been fun to
watch them really take ownership of
everything that's happening and improve
and
go on and play really well in spots.
I think Myles Murphy has really shown a
lot the last couple weeks. You know,
he's been
I don't know anything about the
the scheme or
um what his responsibility is on each
play. I just see him making plays and
impacting the game a lot of different
ways.
Uh you can say that for for a lot of
guys that um
a lot of young guys that are starting to
step up that way. So that's exciting to
see. As a quarterback and not to get the
specifics of the scheme, but is the
scheme something that's impressed you
kind of watching that unfold and
develop? It's hard for me to know really
what they're doing on defense.
Um you know, when I was hurt I was I was
watching the
the defensive tape. Right now I'm not
really doing that.
Um
and so you see certain things here and
there like a pressure or something like
that. Which we've we've certainly
designed some good pressures that
haven't been able to get home and and
pressure the quarterback and and
affect
his decision-making and and cause
mistakes.
Um but it it's hard for me to see that
on the sideline. You you referenced
finding happiness when talking about
player of the week. When you're playing
as well as you did on Sunday, how do you
feel uh coming off the field or like in
the middle of the game about about how
you're feeling like in general when you
have a game like that? Yeah, I felt I
felt good about it for the most part. It
was a clean game.
Um
you know, obviously a couple that you
like back just like every game, but
for the most part I felt good about it.
Joe, I'm sure you get asked this
question every year, but what's your
favorite Christmas gift that you've
gotten?
I don't think I've
had any Christmas gifts yet this year.
No, just Oh, ever?
>> Ever. Ever. When you were little,
recently.
Got a ping pong table from from Santa
uh back this was probably
fifth grade that I got the the ping pong
table. That was sick.
I don't think we've ever asked you this.
I think it's probably due at this point.
Every time you every this time of year
you get a lot of Home Alone references.
How long have that is that been a thing
and what do you make of all of the
Macaulay Culkin comparisons that you've
gotten over the
>> Yeah. Um
Probably probably just since I've been
in the league. Not too many.
Maybe maybe a little in college.
Um
I think I look more like him when he was
a child than right now maybe.
But I I see it. I see it. Is there like
you didn't get it like when you were
growing up but really until you got to
LSU? Not really. Not really. Not that I
remember. Is there any reason why it
just kind of popped up once you got in
the league?
>> know. Yeah. I don't know. Did you like
the movie?
I did like the movie.
So what are you getting gifts planned
for your guys today? Uh yeah, they got
them they got them uh
Monday. Can you tell us about that? No.
That's between us. I mean the same
awards were pretty cool
>> were cool.
>> but you going to top that or Yeah. I
think I did top it this year.
>> Really? You think so? I think I did.
Sick.
What I I hate to get back to the
defense, but just it seems like they've
kind of got on a roll with DJ and Dax on
the outside. I'm wondering if, you know,
how they, you know, maybe stack up to
other corners around the league. Yeah, I
mean I think I think our our defensive
backs been playing well all year.
Obviously DJ
in my opinion has been one of the best
corners in the league this year.
Um and Dax is really coming into his own
I think. Uh
J- JD in the slot has really made some
big plays for us the last couple weeks
since he's been in there. Can't remember
exactly what what the first game that he
was he was in, but
all he's done is made plays. And those
guys are always around the ball making
it difficult and
making tackles
when the guys do catch it. I thought
they've been lights out for the last
you know, eight to 10 weeks. Do you
think DJ should have made the Pro Bowl?
I thought DJ should have made the Pro
Bowl, but
you know, I told him the other day
usually the first year that you should
make it, you're typically an alternate
and then if you stack that year, they
usually give it to you the next year.
It's what happened to to me and a
couple. I kind of see that across the
league a little bit. When you look at
how this year goes in the totality of
it, how much are you going to allow how
injured you were to affect on your
perception on how good the team was?
Does that make sense? Yeah,
um
you know, obviously it played a role.
Obviously it wasn't the
the deciding factor on how the the
season went. It's a it's a team game and
um whoever's out there,
you expect to to play at a high level
and to the standard of
what we built here.
Um
but
you know, as far as what what I can
control,
um
just try to be out there and and affect
the game more. I think last year you
said talked about maybe need to go
outside the box a little bit maybe
improve going on to next year. What is
going outside the box look like?
>> I don't know. We'll see. I don't know.
Um got to figure something out.
The the 20,000 yards, you had said like
you missed more than a year. Yeah, I
didn't know it was I didn't know it was
game based though. Nobody told me that.
You guys all just laugh at me.
What? You all laugh. Cuz it's game it
it was game based. 75 games, not uh
Right.
Not season based. Nobody told me that.
You guys all just let let me make a fool
of myself. Sorry, Joe.
But do you wonder
what's next? What miles do you think of?
40? Do you think of 50? Do you think of
I mean, I I'd like to to play long
enough and
be productive enough that
you know, your name is towards the top
of those lists
year in and year out. So, that's a goal
of mine that is
you know, more of a longevity
thing when you when you get start to get
older and so
that's a goal of mine.
Thanks, guys. Thanks, Joe. Thank you,
Joe.